xomba.com 2012-09-15

# Privacy Policy

Effective May 15, 2006: Updated February 2, 2010: 

About Xomba.com 

Xomba.com is an online service that allows members to set up unique personal profiles that can be linked together through networks of friends. Xomba members may view each other’s profiles, communicate with old friends and meet new friends on the service, as well as share photos, post journals and comments, and describe their interests. To enrich our members' experience, we request and display some personal information, which allows our users to identify each other and expand their network of friends. Xomba members may change their profile information at any time and can control how other members and the service communicates with them. 

Xomba.com cares deeply about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please contact us. 

Information Collection and Use by Xomba.com Xomba.com collects user-submitted information such as name, email address and age to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the Xomba.com service. Xomba.com also collects other profile data including, but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, education and occupation in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other. 

Xomba.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information -- including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data and browser type -- from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website’s services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes. 

User Profile information, including members' pictures and first names, are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the Xomba.com social networking community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join Xomba, to add users to members' friends' networks and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network. Users within a personal network communicate on Xomba.com with each other through the Xomba.com service, without disclosing their email addresses. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, Xomba.com allows users to search for other members using first and last name, email address, and schools and/or companies where users may have attended or worked. 

We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service. Users may choose not to receive email of this type by changing their "notification" setting to "Do not send me notification emails" in the user "Account Settings" 

From time to time, Xomba.com or a partner may sponsor promotions, sweepstakes or contests on Xomba.com. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address, or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply. 

Invitations and Other Communications to Non-members Xomba members may invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. Xomba.com stores the email addresses, which are provided by members. Those who respond to the invitations will be added to the friends list of the person who sent the invitations. Xomba.com does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations or invitation reminders (up to three [3] per email address). Recipients of invitations from Xomba.com may contact Xomba.com to request the removal of their information from our database. 

Use of Cookies Xomba.com uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. However, you must enable cookies from Xomba.com in order to use most functions on the site. Please note that Xomba allows third-party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not Xomba’s Privacy Policy. 

Links Xomba.com contains links to sites. Xomba.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site, a user should read the privacy policy unique to that site. Our privacy policy only governs or applies to information collected on Xomba.com. 

Chat Rooms, Journals and WebLogs, Message Boards, Classifieds and Public Forums Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to Journals, WebLogs, Message Boards, Classifieds or any other Public Forums that that information can be accessed by the public and may in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications. 

Correcting/Updating or Removing Information Xomba.com users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account. 

Email Choice/Opt-out Members who no longer wish to receive updates or notifications may choose not to by selecting “Do not send me notification emails” in the user profile “Account Settings.” Users who do not wish to receive Xomba.com newsletters may choose not to by selecting “Do not send me Xomba newsletters” in the user profile “Account Settings.” All notification emails and Xomba.com newsletters also include the above instructions for opting-out of those communications in the future. 

Third-Party Advertising Ads appearing on this website may be delivered to users by Xomba.com or one of our web advertising partners. Our web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad servers to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Xomba.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use (share) information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice or to become informed of your options regarding preventing these companies from using your information, click [ here ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). We use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information (e.g., the pages you visit and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our website. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third-party web beacon to collect this information. If you would like more information about this practice or to become informed of your options regarding preventing these companies from using your information, click [ here ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) (link to the NAI universal user opt-out). 

Security Xomba.com member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. Xomba.com takes precautions to ensure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. 

Sharing and Disclosure of Information Xomba.com Collects Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, Xomba will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by Xomba.com, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce Xomba.com’s Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. Xomba reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Xomba or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below. 

Changes in Our Privacy Policy From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it and when we may disclose it. A user is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify users by posting a notice on our website for 30 days. 

Contacting the Web Site If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at: services(at)xomba(dot)com, Xomba, Inc. PMB #102, 1650 Margaret St., Ste. 302, Jacksonville, FL, 32204-3869.
